# PETRA COTOCIU

## **PERSONAL PROFILE:**

Digital strategist and go-getter, with analytical thinking and a big chunk of creativity and enthusiasm. Experience in performance analysis, business planning, understanding consumers needs and e-business gained during my one year long placement in a digital marketing agency.

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

- Creative and Critical Thinking
- Market research
- Project Management
- Social Media

# **CONTACT DETAILS:**

69 Lorne Road, Bath, BA2 3BZ Phone: 07737734148 petra.cotociu@gmail.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

## STRATEGY CONSULTANT

The Mars Agency November 2020- December 2020

- Dcomm market research for Mars Wrigley Confectionery UK
- Analysis of the e-commerce and digital marketing strategies in the FMCG industry

#### SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER

The Creator Concept July 2020- present

- Influencer management
- Content planning for business social media platforms
- Copywriting and translating DE-ENG

#### **ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT AND STRATEGY TRAINEE**

Iris Germany GmbH Munich June 2019-June 2020

- Conducting the analysis of key engagement rates and reports for advertising campaigns
- Value propositions and brand positionings development for the agencies largest B2C client
- Competitor and best-practice research
- Developing the business ethics guidelines
- Preparing and facilitating social media branding workshops
- Project management and coordination of internal departments
- Maintaining 3rd party supplier communication
- Setting up cost proposals, invoices and keeping track of the financial status of projects

## **BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP**

Solexpert Company June 2018- August 2018

- Writing articles for the supplier's online newsletter
- Researching potential suppliers and performing quality checks

# **EDUCATION:**

## UNIVERSITY OF BATH (2017-2021)

BSc (hons) International Management and Modern Languages (German)

E-business

Economics of strategy: rivalry
Entrepreneurship and Innovation
International Marketing Management
Accounting and Decision making for managers
Advanced Consumer Behaviour
Change Management

## **RELEVANT SKILLS:**

Fluent in English, German and Romanian Good command of Google Analytics and SEMrush Efficienct in a fast-pased work environment Strong attention to details Good command of Microsoft Office Suite Collaborative nature